Register of the Dixy Lee Ray papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- PHOTOGRAPHS., 1863 prints, 12 postcards, 112 negatives, 109 slides / 135 envelopes, 1 oversize box, 7 slide boxes. (Othertype 10.A-V)
  - 4 prints depicting the ash fall from Mount St. Helens., July 1980 (Folder DJ)
  - 9 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at the construction start of the MOD-2, Bonneville Power Administration, with Warren G. Magnuson and Mike McCormack., undated (Folder DK)
  - 7 prints of Dixy Lee Ray with participants of the Northern Tier Conference held in the Governor's Mansion., undated (Folder DL)
  - 7 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at Officers' Wives' Club reception., September 1978 (Folder DM)
  - 7 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at the Olympic Hotel., undated (Folder DN)
  - 12 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at the Port Dock dinner in Camas, WA., August 27, 1980 (Folder DO)
  - 23 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at a reception at the Governor's Mansion., undated (Folder DP)
  - 32 prints of Dixy Lee Ray flying to California and watching the Rose Bowl football game., 1979 (Folder DQ)
  - 4 prints depicting the Capitol in Olympia., undated (Folder DR)
  - 25 prints of Dixy Lee Ray swearing-in State patrol officers., undated (Folder DS-DT)
  - 27 prints of Dixy Lee Ray in Taiwan and Japan., October 1977 (Folder DU)
  - 15 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at Town Hall meetings., undated (Folder DV)
  - 16 prints of Dixy Lee Ray with Veterans, undated (Folder DW)
  - 4 prints depicting Dixy Lee Ray addressing the Wisconsin Power and Light Company, on two different occasions., undated (Folder DX)
  - 28 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at Christmas parties., undated (Folder DY-DZ)
  - 6 prints of Dixy Lee Ray and her sister Marion Reid posing in front of the Capitol in Olympia for their Christmas card., undated (Folder EA)
  - 4 prints of Dixy Lee Ray with President Carter and Vice President Mondale., undated (Folder EB)
  - 5 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at the Argonne National Laboratory., May 1981 (Folder EC)
  - 25 prints of Dixy Lee Ray and other people (miscellanea), undated (Folder ED)
  - 112 negatives of Dixy Lee Ray, undated (Folder EE)
  - 30 oversize prints of Dixy Lee Ray (miscellanea), undated (Folder fEF)
- SLIDES. (Cabinet Slide cabinet)
  - 5 slides of Dixy Lee Ray's appearance on television for the 1974 Woman of the Year Award. (Folder 1)
  - 33 slides depicting the CAPCO (Central Area Power Coordination Group) power plants, Pennsylvania. (Folder 2-3)
  - 71 slides of Dixy Lee Ray posing as Governor in her office. (Folder 4-7)
- STATE DEPARTMENT MATERIALS
  - Discussion paper on safeguards and export controls - British meeting, CONFIDENTIAL, 10 June 1975
  - Memorandum for all American diplomatic posts from the State Department entitled "The Challenge of the Developing Countries: New Demands for Power and Participation." CONFIDENTIAL
  - Memorandum for DLR from William Sullivan, Jr. re program and resources plan. CONFIDENTIAL
  - Memorandum for the Chief of naval operations from the Department of the Navy. CONFIDENTIAL, RESTRICTED DATA (CLASSIFIED BY AEC-DOD CLASSIFICATION)
  - Memorandum for the President from Jim Cannon re providing additional U.S. uranium capacity. CONFIDENTIAL
  - Memorandum of conversation to NPT backstopping group, re regional reprocessing in Asia. CONFIDENTIAL
  - Note entitled "Issues of Concern to the State Department on Implementing the UEA Decision." CONFIDENTIAL
  - Note for DLR re the responsabilities of the Office of the Deputy Assistant Secretary for Technology, OES. OFFICIAL USE ONLY
  - Study entitled "The Multinational Approach." SECRET
  - Telegrams re nuclear safeguards in Brazil. LIMITED OFFICIAL USE and CONFIDENTIAL
- INCREMENTAL MATERIALS (Box 186-190)
- DECLASSIFIED U.S. GOVERNMENT DOCUMENTS RELEASED IN 2014 (Box 190)
  - Office of the Director of Defense Research and Engineering, Defense Science Board memoranda, reports, and other materials, 1976
  - draft, Oak Ridge National Laboratory and the U.S. Atomic Energy Commission, 1970
- DECLASSIFIED U.S. GOVERNMENT DOCUMENTS RELEASED IN 2017, 1972-1975